oh damn check that out what is that oh I
didn't know they made them like that I
don't even understand what I'm seeing oh
I would love to see what's under there I
am really curious about that I mean I
have no idea well you know we we
obviously have some idea you know I
don't well you know it's uh you know
it's a coochie baby yeah or something
nah man is definitely her lady parts
Oh maybe it's just more skin no it's a
vagina
yeah or maybe it's a little face under
there
no no is it's definitely gonna be a
vagina why but because she's a girl and
girls have vaginas man what is that what
is a vagina it's a woman's reproductive
organ what are you being serious right
now
thank you rattles all I require
[Music]